A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1961
  - United States, 1961/200
    - University of California (D-K) (Reel 27, Frame 908)
    - University of California (L-R) (Reel 27, Frame 1023)
    - University of California (S-W) (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - University of Chicago (A-W) (Reel 28, Frame 256)
    - University of Florida (C-W) (Reel 28, Frame 606)
    - University of Hawaii (A-W) (Reel 28, Frame 764)
    - University (C-H) (Reel 28, Frame 823)
    - University of Illinois (A-U) (Reel 28, Frame 927)
    - University (I-L) (Reel 28, Frame 1061)
    - University of Michigan (B-W) (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - University (M) (Reel 29, Frame 214)
    - University of Notre Dame (B-S) (Reel 29, Frame 394)
    - University (N) (Reel 29, Frame 507)
    - University of Oregon, International Studies (Mikesell) (Reel 29, Frame 645)
    - University of Oregon (A-T) (Reel 29, Frame 817)
    - University of Pennsylvania (C-S) (Reel 29, Frame 947)
    - University of Pittsburgh (B-S) (Reel 29, Frame 1021)
    - University (O-R) (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - University of Washington (K-S) (Reel 30, Frame 114)
    - University of Wisconsin (A-Y) (Reel 30, Frame 207)
    - University (S-W) (Reel 30, Frame 330)
    - U (Reel 30, Frame 453)
    - V (Reel 30, Frame 483)
    - Washington University (A-W) (Reel 30, Frame 717)
    - Wayne State University (A-W) (Reel 30, Frame 757)
    - Wa (Reel 30, Frame 827)
    - We (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - Wh-Wilm (Reel 31, Frame 93)
    - Wils (Reel 31, Frame 220)
    - Wim-Wr (Reel 31, Frame 414)
    - Yale University (A-W) (Reel 31, Frame 507)
    - Y-Z (Reel 31, Frame 747)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1961/200.A
      - A-T (Reel 31, Frame 760)
      - University (A-M) (Reel 31, Frame 940)
      - University (N-W) (Reel 32, Frame 1)
      - V-Y (Reel 32, Frame 184)
    - United States - Nursing, 1961/200.C
      - Wayne State University (Walker) (Reel 32, Frame 260)
      - C-W (Reel 32, Frame 403)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/200.D
      - I-U (Reel 32, Frame 560)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1961/200.E
      - B-W (Reel 32, Frame 672)
    - United States - Declinations, 1961/200.F
      - B-S (Reel 32, Frame 688)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1961/200.R
      - A-W (Reel 32, Frame 700)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1961/200.S
      - A-Y (Reel 32, Frame 883)
    - United States - Virus Studies, 1961/200.V
      - American Committee on Arthropod-borne Viruses (Reel 33, Frame 1)
      - A-J (Reel 33, Frame 316)
  - New York, 1961/235
    - 235 (Reel 33, Frame 337)
  - Ohio, 1961/238
    Ohio
    - 238 (Reel 33, Frame 342)
  - Philippines, 1961/242
    - A-V (Reel 33, Frame 344)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1961/242.A
      - U (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/242.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 34, Frame 19)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, 1961/242.E
      - 242E (Reel 34, Frame 21)
      - B-V (Reel 34, Frame 31)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1961/242.R
      - University of the Philippines (Reel 34, Frame 66)
    - Philippines - Virus Studies, 1961/242.V
      - University of the Philippines (Reel 34, Frame 112)
  - Puerto Rico, 1961/243
    - B-V (Reel 34, Frame 114)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1961/243.A
      - University of Puerto Rico (Medical School) (Reel 34, Frame 283)
    - Puerto Rico - Fellowships, 1961/243.E
      - Baez, Alberto (Reel 34, Frame 338)
  - Tennessee, 1961/248
    Tennessee
    - 248 (Reel 34, Frame 345)
  - South America, 1961/300
    - 300 (Reel 34, Frame 347)
    - Administration (Reel 34, Frame 418)
    - A-L (Reel 34, Frame 760)
    - South America - Nursing, 1961/300.C
      - 300C (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1961/300.S
      - Public Administration (Reel 35, Frame 9)
  - Argentina, 1961/301
    - 301 (Reel 35, Frame 158)
    - A-U (Reel 35, Frame 168)
    - Argentina - Nursing, 1961/301.C
      - National University of Litoral (Nursing School) (Reel 35, Frame 549)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/301.D
      - A-U (Reel 35, Frame 555)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, 1961/301.E
      - C-R (Reel 35, Frame 562)
    - Argentina - Humanities and Arts, 1961/301.R
      - Libraries (Reel 35, Frame 585)
    - Argentina - Social Sciences, 1961/301.S
      - Economics (Reel 35, Frame 587)
  - Bolivia, 1961/303
    - B-U (Reel 35, Frame 589)
    - Bolivia - Medical Sciences, 1961/303.A
      - University of San Simon (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 607)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, 1961/303.E
      - C-M (Reel 35, Frame 682)
  - Brazil, 1961/305
    - 305 (Reel 35, Frame 693)
    - A-C (Reel 35, Frame 718)
    - D-R (Reel 35, Frame 880)
    - University of Rio Grande (A-S) (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - S-Z (Reel 36, Frame 201)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1961/305.A
      - U (Reel 36, Frame 434)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1961/305.C
      - 305C (Reel 36, Frame 526)
      - S-U (Reel 36, Frame 530)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/305.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 36, Frame 582)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1961/305.E
      - 305E (Reel 36, Frame 606)
      - A-W (Reel 36, Frame 620)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, 1961/305.S
      - C-U (Reel 36, Frame 786)
  - Chile, 1961/309
    - 309 (Reel 36, Frame 796)
    - A-V (Reel 36, Frame 876)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1961/309.A
      - University of Chile (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1961/309.C
      - 309C (Reel 37, Frame 26)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/309.D
      - Agriculture (Sandoval, Orlando) (Reel 37, Frame 28)
    - Chile - Fellowships, 1961/309.E
      - 309E (Reel 37, Frame 39)
      - C-U (Reel 37, Frame 43)
    - Chile - Humanities and Arts, 1961/309.R
      - C-U (Reel 37, Frame 58)
    - Chile - Social Sciences, 1961/309.S
      - E-U (Reel 37, Frame 70)
  - Colombia, 1961/311
    - 311 (Reel 37, Frame 82)
    - A-G (Reel 37, Frame 149)
    - I-O (Reel 37, Frame 297)
    - P-V (Reel 37, Frame 464)
    - Universidad del Valle (A-S) (Reel 37, Frame 586)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1961/311.A
      - C-U (Reel 37, Frame 769)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/311.D
      - Agricultural Education (Reel 37, Frame 877)
      - A-U (Reel 37, Frame 1076)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, 1961/311.E
      - 311E (Reel 38, Frame 1)
      - A-V (Reel 38, Frame 19)
  - Costa Rica, 1961/313
    - E-U (Reel 38, Frame 170)
    - Costa Rica - Medical Sciences, 1961/313.A
      - University of Costa Rica (Reel 38, Frame 239)
    - Costa Rica - Nursing, 1961/313.C
      - National School of Nursing, San Jose (Reel 38, Frame 252)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, 1961/313.E
      - Carboni Escalante, Fernando (Reel 38, Frame 259)
  - Cuba, 1961/315
    - A-M (Reel 38, Frame 262)
    - Cuba - Nursing, 1961/315.C
      - 315C (Reel 38, Frame 267)
  - Ecuador, 1961/317
    - A-U (Reel 38, Frame 269)
    - Ecuador - Medical Sciences, 1961/317.A
      - University of Ecuador (Medical Faculty) (Reel 38, Frame 321)
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/317.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 38, Frame 342)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, 1961/317.E
      - A-R (Reel 38, Frame 348)
  - Guatemala, 1961/319
    - B-W (Reel 38, Frame 372)
    - Guatemala - Medical Sciences, 1961/319.A
      - University of San Carlos (Medical School) (Reel 38, Frame 424)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/319.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 38, Frame 429)
    - Guatemala - Fellowships, 1961/319.E
      - Iturbide, Angel (Reel 38, Frame 436)
  - Haiti, 1961/320
    - H-W (Reel 38, Frame 441)
  - Honduras, 1961/321
    - S-U (Reel 38, Frame 448)
    - Escuela Agricola Panamericana (Reel 38, Frame 476)
    - Honduras - Medical Sciences, 1961/321.A
      - University of Honduras (Medical School) (Reel 38, Frame 668)
    - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/321.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 38, Frame 676)
    - Honduras - Fellowships, 1961/321.E
      - Fernandez, Fernando (Reel 38, Frame 678)
  - Mexico, 1961/323
    - 323 (Reel 38, Frame 683)
    - A-C (Reel 38, Frame 705)
    - D-G (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - H-O (Reel 39, Frame 130)
    - P-Z (Reel 39, Frame 289)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1961/323.A
      - N-U (Reel 39, Frame 475)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1961/323.E
      - 323E (Reel 39, Frame 597)
      - A-V (Reel 39, Frame 607)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1961/323.R
      - University (M-N) (Reel 39, Frame 673)
  - Nicaragua, 1961/325
    - C-U (Reel 39, Frame 707)
    - Nicaragua - Medical Sciences, 1961/325.A
      - University of Nicaragua (Medical School) (Reel 39, Frame 742)
    - Nicaragua - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/325.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 39, Frame 755)
  - Republic of Panama, 1961/327
    Panama Canal (Panama) -- Law and legislation
    - A-U (Reel 39, Frame 757)
    - Republic of Panama - Medical Sciences, 1961/327.A
      - University of Panama (Medical School) (Reel 39, Frame 805)
  - Paraguay, 1961/329
    - Paraguay - Medical Sciences, 1961/329.A
      - University of Asuncion (Medical School) (Reel 39, Frame 809)
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/329.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 39, Frame 826)
  - Peru, 1961/331
    - A-U (Reel 39, Frame 828)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/331.D
      - A (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - Peru - Fellowships, 1961/331.E
      - C-S (Reel 40, Frame 27)
  - El Salvador, 1961/333
    - H-U (Reel 40, Frame 42)
    - El Salvador - Nursing, 1961/333.C
      - National School of Nursing, Salvador (Reel 40, Frame 77)
    - El Salvador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/333.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 40, Frame 80)
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, 1961/333.E
      - B-S (Reel 40, Frame 94)
  - Dominican Republic, 1961/335
    Dominican Republic
    - P (Reel 40, Frame 112)
  - Uruguay, 1961/337
    - B-U (Reel 40, Frame 115)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/337.D
      - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 202)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, 1961/337.E
      - B-R (Reel 40, Frame 258)
  - Venezuela, 1961/339
    - B-W (Reel 40, Frame 283)
    - Venezuela - Medical Sciences, 1961/339.A
      - U (Reel 40, Frame 337)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/339.D
      - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 341)
    - Venezuela - Declinations, 1961/339.F
      - University of Venezuela (Library) (Reel 40, Frame 362)
    - Venezuela - Virus Studies, 1961/339.V
      - 339V (Reel 40, Frame 364)
  - Great Britain, 1961/400
    - C (Reel 40, Frame 384)
  - England, 1961/401
    - A-J (Reel 40, Frame 391)
    - L-M (Reel 40, Frame 758)
    - N-R (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - S-W (Reel 41, Frame 292)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1961/401.A
      - U (Reel 41, Frame 634)
    - England - Fellowships, 1961/401.E
      - A-W (Reel 41, Frame 636)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1961/401.R
      - B-U (Reel 41, Frame 697)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1961/401.S
      - Nuffield College (B-C) (Reel 41, Frame 701)
  - Ireland, 1961/403
    - M-W (Reel 41, Frame 707)
    - Ireland - Fellowships, 1961/403.E
      - G-J (Reel 41, Frame 737)
  - Scotland, 1961/405
    - R-U (Reel 41, Frame 774)
    - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1961/405.S
      - University of Edinburgh (Social Anthropology) (Reel 41, Frame 828)
  - Wales, 1961/407
    - G-U (Reel 41, Frame 846)
  - Australia, 1961/410
    - 410 (Reel 41, Frame 856)
    - A-W (Reel 41, Frame 859)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1961/410.A
      - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - Australia - Nursing, 1961/410.C
      - 410C (Reel 42, Frame 38)
      - C-R (Reel 42, Frame 41)
    - Australia - Fellowships, 1961/410.E
      - B-O (Reel 42, Frame 46)
  - New Zealand, 1961/418
    - C-W (Reel 42, Frame 55)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1961/418.A
      - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 80)
    - New Zealand - Nursing, 1961/418.C
      - 418C (Reel 42, Frame 85)
      - N-V (Reel 42, Frame 92)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, 1961/418.E
      - Veale, Arthur M. O. (Reel 42, Frame 98)
  - Fiji, 1961/419
    - Dill-Russell, P. W. (Reel 42, Frame 106)
    - Fiji - Medical Sciences, 1961/419.A
      - Central Medical School (Reel 42, Frame 108)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1961/420
    - Confederation of Central American Universities (Reel 42, Frame 112)
    - C-M (Reel 42, Frame 395)
  - Guyana, 1961/423
    - B-G (Reel 42, Frame 502)
    - Guyana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/423.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 42, Frame 520)
  - British Honduras, 1961/425
    - Education (Reel 42, Frame 523)
  - Canada, 1961/427
    - A-M (Reel 42, Frame 577)
    - N-Y (Reel 42, Frame 978)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1961/427.A
      - M-U (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1961/427.C
      - M-U (Reel 43, Frame 91)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1961/427.S
      - Social Science Research Council of Canada (Reel 43, Frame 117)
  - Jamaica, 1961/437
    - B-W (Reel 43, Frame 121)
    - Jamaica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/439.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 43, Frame 287)
  - Trinidad, 1961/451
    - A-U (Reel 43, Frame 294)
    - Trinidad - Fellowships, 1961/451.E
      - D-G (Reel 43, Frame 389)
  - Ceylon, 1961/462
    - A-U (Reel 43, Frame 403)
    - Ceylon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/462.D
      - University of Ceylon (Agriculture) (Reel 43, Frame 446)
    - Ceylon - Fellowships, 1961/462.E
      - O-S (Reel 43, Frame 450)
    - Ceylon - Humanities and Arts, 1961/462.R
      - Drama (Reel 43, Frame 457)
  - Hong Kong, 1961/463
    - H-U (Reel 43, Frame 484)
  - India, 1961/464
    - 464 (Reel 43, Frame 554)
    - Aa-Al (Reel 43, Frame 583)
    - Am-Bal (Reel 43, Frame 746)
    - Ban-Bu (Reel 43, Frame 877)
    - C-E (Reel 44, Frame 1)
      Scope and Contents
      File "464 / Demographic Training and Research Center, Bombay" (Reel 44, Frame 200) includes correspondence and reports related to Dr. C. Chandrasekaran and Dr. Katherine Kuder; including "The Organization and Case-Load of Family Planning Clinics in Greater Bombay" (1961) by Dr. C. Chandrasekaran and Dr. Katherine Kuder, Demographic Training and Research Centre, Chembur, Bombay, India.
    - Finance (Reel 44, Frame 281)
    - G-H (Reel 44, Frame 470)
    - Indian (A-S) (Reel 44, Frame 596)
    - Institute of Economic Growth (Agarwala) (Reel 44, Frame 718)
    - I-M (Reel 44, Frame 921)
    - N-O (Reel 44, Frame 1069)
    - P (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - R (Reel 45, Frame 47)
    - S (Reel 45, Frame 100)
    - T-Y (Reel 45, Frame 347)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1961/464.A
      - A-V (Reel 45, Frame 604)
    - India - Nursing, 1961/464.C
      - 464C (Reel 45, Frame 683)
      - A-V (Reel 45, Frame 694)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/464.D
      - A-U (Reel 45, Frame 748)
    - India - Fellowships, 1961/464.E
      - 464E (Reel 45, Frame 852)
      - A-W (Reel 45, Frame 861)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1961/464.R
      - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 1)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1961/464.S
      - I-U (Reel 46, Frame 16)
    - India - Virus Studies, 1961/464.V
      - Lucknow University (Reel 46, Frame 131)
  - Pakistan, 1961/465
    - 465 (Reel 46, Frame 146)
    - Pakistan - Medical Sciences, 1961/465.A
      - Khyber Medical College (Reel 46, Frame 356)
    - Pakistan - Nursing, 1961/465.C
      - 465C (Reel 46, Frame 360)
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/465.D
      - A-N (Reel 46, Frame 363)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, 1961/465.E
      - 465E (Reel 46, Frame 377)
      - A-M (Reel 46, Frame 379)
    - Pakistan - Humanities and Arts, 1961/465.R
      - H-U (Reel 46, Frame 404)
    - Pakistan - Social Sciences, 1961/465.S
      - I-U (Reel 46, Frame 462)
  - Burma, 1961/468
    - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 483)
    - Burma - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/468.D
      - Agriculture (Kyu) (Reel 46, Frame 488)
  - Iraq, 1961/470
    - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 490)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1961/472
    - Porter, Judith A. (Reel 46, Frame 519)
  - Malaysia, 1961/473
    - 473 (Reel 46, Frame 524)
    - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 532)
    - Malaysia - Medical Sciences, 1961/473.A
      - I-U (Reel 46, Frame 574)
  - Nepal, 1961/474
    - L-S (Reel 46, Frame 611)
  - Africa, 1961/475
    - 475 (Reel 46, Frame 626)
    - Commission for Technical Cooperation in Africa (Reel 46, Frame 628)
    - E-P (Reel 46, Frame 838)
    - Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/475.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 46, Frame 967)
    - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1961/475.R
      - E-L (Reel 46, Frame 985)
  - Kenya, 1961/476
    - 476 (Reel 46, Frame 1015)
    - A-R (Reel 46, Frame 1019)
    - Kenya - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/476.D
      - Agriculture (A-S) (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, 1961/476.E
      - D-N (Reel 47, Frame 23)
  - East Africa Region, 1961/477
    - B-V (Reel 47, Frame 26)
  - Rhodesia, 1961/483
    - 483 (Reel 47, Frame 64)
    - A-U (Reel 47, Frame 73)
    - Rhodesia - Medical Sciences, 1961/483.A
      - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland (Reel 47, Frame 216)
    - Rhodesia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/483.D
      - A-U (Reel 47, Frame 230)
    - Rhodesia - Fellowships, 1961/483.E
      - Shelbourne, C. T. A. (Reel 47, Frame 258)
    - Rhodesia - Social Sciences, 1961/483.S
      - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland (Economics) (Reel 47, Frame 263)
  - North Africa Region, 1961/485
    - University of Algiers (Reel 47, Frame 279)
  - South Africa Region, 1961/487
    - B-W (Reel 47, Frame 281)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1961/489
    - 489 (Reel 47, Frame 317)
    - B-V (Reel 47, Frame 327)
    - Cape of Good Hope - Fellowships, 1961/489.E
      - Matshikiza, Todd T. (Reel 47, Frame 392)
  - Uganda, 1961/492
    - E-Z (Reel 47, Frame 442)
    - Uganda - Medical Sciences, 1961/492.A
      - Makerere College (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 504)
    - Uganda - Nursing, 1961/492.C
      - 492C (Reel 47, Frame 580)
    - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/492.D
      - Agriculture (Mukasa) (Reel 47, Frame 582)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, 1961/492.E
      - Waddimba, George (Reel 47, Frame 584)
  - Sudan, 1961/494
    - 494 (Reel 47, Frame 596)
    - C-U (Reel 47, Frame 599)
  - West Africa, 1961/495
    - 495 (Reel 47, Frame 662)
    - C-Z (Reel 47, Frame 666)
    - University of Ghana (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 681)
    - West Africa - Medical Sciences, 1961/495.A
      - University of Ghana (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 681)
  - Ghana, 1961/496
    - 496 (Reel 47, Frame 684)
    - A-U (Reel 47, Frame 686)
    - Ghana - Medical Sciences, 1961/496.A
      - University College of Ghana (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 974)
    - Ghana - Nursing, 1961/496.C
      - 496C (Reel 47, Frame 981)
    - Ghana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/496.D
      - Agriculture (Botsio) (Reel 47, Frame 1019)
    - Ghana - Fellowships, 1961/496.E
      - A-Q (Reel 47, Frame 1033)
    - Ghana - Humanities and Arts, 1961/496.R
      - Music (Reel 47, Frame 1067)
  - Nigeria, 1961/497
    - 497 (Reel 47, Frame 1069)
    - A-E (Reel 48, Frame 1)
    - H-N (Reel 48, Frame 112)
    - University College, Ibadan (D-W) (Reel 48, Frame 244)
    - O-W (Reel 48, Frame 448)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1961/497.A
      - M-U (Reel 48, Frame 657)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/497.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 48, Frame 673)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, 1961/497.E
      - A-U (Reel 48, Frame 692)
    - Nigeria - Social Sciences, 1961/497.S
      - University College, Ibadan (Sociology) (Reel 48, Frame 741)
  - Sierra Leone, 1961/499
    - U-W (Reel 48, Frame 752)
    - Sierra Leone - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/499.D
      - Agriculture (Bakshi) (Reel 48, Frame 791)
    - Sierra Leone - Fellowships, 1961/499.E
      - C (Reel 48, Frame 795)
  - France, 1961/500
    - A-Z (Reel 48, Frame 821)
    - France - Fellowships, 1961/500.E
      - D-N (Reel 48, Frame 1129)
  - Algeria, 1961/501
    - 501 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
    - Algeria - Fellowships, 1961/501.E
      - Tchanderli, Djamal (Reel 49, Frame 3)
  - Vietnam, 1961/509
    - H-U (Reel 49, Frame 12)
    - Vietnam - Fellowships, 1961/509.E
      - P-T (Reel 49, Frame 18)
  - French Guinea, 1961/525.E
    - Camara, Silvain (Reel 49, Frame 37)
  - Ivory Coast, 1961/527
    - 527 (Reel 49, Frame 40)
    - B-I (Reel 49, Frame 87)
    - Ivory Coast - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/527.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 49, Frame 108)
    - Ivory Coast - Humanities and Arts, 1961/527.R
      - Drama (Gadeau) (Reel 49, Frame 122)
  - Mali, 1961/530
    - E-T (Reel 49, Frame 129)
  - Senegal, 1961/531
    - L-U (Reel 49, Frame 146)
    - Senegal - Fellowships, 1961/531.E
      - Sy, Moussa O. (Reel 49, Frame 251)
  - Tunis, 1961/539
    Tunisia
    - C-U (Reel 49, Frame 289)
    - Tunis - Fellowships, 1961/539.E
      - Rachid, Ben (Reel 49, Frame 309)
  - Asia, 1961/600
    - Administration (Reel 49, Frame 311)
    - Administration (A) (Reel 49, Frame 478)
    - Listed Mail (Reel 49, Frame 695)
    - Asia - Fellowships, 1961/600.E
      - 600E (Reel 49, Frame 777)
  - China, 1961/601
    - 601 (Reel 49, Frame 779)
    - C-W (Reel 49, Frame 786)
  - Taiwan, 1961/605
    - A-W (Reel 49, Frame 807)
    - Taiwan - Fellowships, 1961/605.E
      - W (Reel 49, Frame 900)
  - Japan, 1961/609
    - 609 (Reel 49, Frame 906)
    - A-G (Reel 50, Frame 1)
    - H-I (Reel 50, Frame 114)
    - J-M (Reel 50, Frame 305)
    - N-S (Reel 50, Frame 563)
    - T-Y (Reel 50, Frame 924)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1961/609.A
      - C-T (Reel 51, Frame 1)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1961/609.C
      - S-T (Reel 51, Frame 23)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/609.D
      - A-H (Reel 51, Frame 43)
    - Japan - Fellowships, 1961/609.E
      - 609E (Reel 51, Frame 104)
      - A-W (Reel 51, Frame 116)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1961/609.R
      - K-T (Reel 51, Frame 321)
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1961/609.S
      - K-S (Reel 51, Frame 329)
  - Korea, 1961/613
    - C-Y (Reel 51, Frame 337)
    - Korea - Fellowships, 1961/613.E
      - Ahn, Byong-ik (Reel 51, Frame 514)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1961/613.R
      - 613R (Reel 51, Frame 519)
  - Thailand, 1961/617
    - C-U (Reel 51, Frame 521)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1961/617.A
      - U (Reel 51, Frame 587)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/617.D
      - Agriculture (C-P) (Reel 51, Frame 598)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1961/617.E
      - 617E (Reel 51, Frame 607)
      - C-K (Reel 51, Frame 610)
  - Southeast Asia, 1961/617
    - Southeast Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/625.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 51, Frame 624)
    - Southeast Asia - Fellowships, 1961/625.E
      - 625E (Reel 51, Frame 650)
  - Holland, 1961/650
    - B-W (Reel 51, Frame 652)
    - Holland - Fellowships, 1961/650.E
      - Leibrandt, Gottfried J. (Reel 51, Frame 746)
  - Indonesia, 1961/652
    - A-J (Reel 51, Frame 761)
    - K-Z (Reel 52, Frame 1)
    - Indonesia - Medical Sciences, 1961/652.A
      - A-U (Reel 52, Frame 203)
    - Indonesia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1961/652.D
      - Andalas University (Agriculture) (Reel 52, Frame 248)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1961/652.E
      - 652E (Reel 52, Frame 254)
      - B-Y (Reel 52, Frame 283)
  - Colony of North Borneo, 1961/653
    Malaysia - Sabah
    - Education (Reel 52, Frame 304)
  - Surinam, 1961/659
    - Health (Reel 52, Frame 341)
  - Europe, 1961/700
    - E (Reel 52, Frame 351)
  - Ethiopia, 1961/701
    - 701 (Reel 52, Frame 357)
    - G-Y (Reel 52, Frame 365)
    - Ethiopia - Fellowships, 1961/701.E
      - H-S (Reel 52, Frame 428)
  - Afghanistan, 1961/703